Guide to the Amos Poe Papers, 1966-2005 MSS.203
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Photography
  - Series VI, Subseries D: Personal
    - "Circus Slides", undated (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - [Dr. M. Brennan], December 1975 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - "4 - 1 - 83", 1983 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - [High School, Etc.], various (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - "In My Truck...Color '72", 1972 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - "Italy '81 Show", 1981 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - "Italy '81 Outakes", 1981 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - "Lesson 12 - 18, 2nd Roll 10, 12," "2pm," "4pm," "6pm," and "Lesson 35", undated (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - "March 1, 1990" (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - "May 1973" (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - "May 1980" (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - [1912 Husband and Wife Portrait] (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - "RTE 6 - A, North Trurd, Cape Cod '82", 1982 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - " '72 Airport Madness Color", 1972 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - "Ticket to Ride", undated (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - "To Amos the 'Super,' Noel 'Lois Lane' Neill", undated (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - "TV Party 'Driven' ", undated (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - [Untitled Contact Sheets and Negatives], December 6, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - "Vermont '72 Color", 1972 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - "Xerox #1", undated (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - [Various Unidentified Photographic Elements, 1 of 3], undated (Box 34)
    - [Various Unidentified Photographic Elements, 2 of 3], undated (Box 35)
    - [Various Unidentified Photographic Elements, 3 of 3], undated (Box 36)
    - 2016 Accretion: Photographs, circa 1989 (Box 31, Folder 41)
- Series VII: Visual Materials
  - Series VII, Subseries A: Scrapbooks
    - Memoirs of a Lens (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook Materials, various (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook Materials, various (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook Materials, various (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Scrapbook Materials [Gold Floral Photo Album], undated (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Scrapbook, 1978-79 (Box 38)
      Scope and Content
      This box includes a notebook and 2 folders of loose elements that have been encapsulated in mylar along with a print out of a photo of the page in which they belong.
    - Scrapbook, 1978-79 (Box 39)
      This box includes a notebook and a folder of loose elements that have been encapsulated in mylar along with a print out of a photo of the page in which they belong.
- Series VIII: Film
  - Series VIII, Subseries A: Access Copies
    Conditions Governing Access
    Access copies for some materials are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
    - [1]-- Ballad of a Thin Woman [2]-- Knife in the Rain, [1972]; ID: 203.0102 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0102)
      Format: 16mm
      Color, Silent
      Duration: [00:23:00]
      Original Format: Super8mm
    - [1]-- St. Mark's Place Massacre [2]-- Ark of Destiny, [1972]; ID: 203.0099 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0099)
      Duration: [00:23:10]
    - My, My Michaelangelo, 1974; ID: 203.0226 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0226)
      Color, Sound
      Duration: 00:09:27
      Original Format: 16mm
  - Series VIII, Subseries B: Originals
    Access copies may not be available for consultation, please ask a Fales archivist.
    - ["Aerosmith" through "Chinese, Etc."], undated; ID: 203.0191 - 203.0202 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0191 - 203.0202)
      Duration: [unknown]
    - 1) Ballad of a Thin Woman 2) Knife in the Rain, undated; ID: 203.0001 (Case 203.0001)
      Format: Super 8mm
    - 1) Ballad of a Thin Woman 2) Knife in the Rain -- [Internegative], undated; ID: 203.0100A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0100A)
    - 1) Ballad of a Thin Woman 2) Knife in the Rain -- [Internegative Answer Print], undated; ID: 203.0101 (Reel 203.0101)
    - 1) Ballad of a Thin Woman 2) Knife in the Rain -- [Release Print], undated; ID: 203.0102 (Box Shared Fales 048, Reel 203.0102)
    - The Blank Generation, undated; ID: 203.0008A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0008A)
    - The Blank Generation, undated; ID: 203.0009A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0009A)
    - The Blank Generation -- [Mag Track], undated; ID: 203.0118 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0118)
    - The Blank Generation -- Outtakes #1, undated; ID: 203.0106 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0106)
    - The Blank Generation -- Outtakes #2, undated; ID: 203.0107 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0107)
    - The Blank Generation -- Outtakes #3, undated; ID: 203.0108 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0108)
    - The Blank Generation, Pt. 1 [B + W Workprint], undated; ID: 203.0114A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0114A)
    - The Blank Generation, Pt. 1 [B Track], undated; ID: 203.0115 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0115)
    - The Blank Generation, Pt. 2 [B Track], undated; ID: 203.0117 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0117)
    - The Blank Generation, Pt. 2 [B + W Workprint], undated; ID: 203.0116A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0116A)
    - Blue Eyes -- [Pix], undated; ID: 203.0056 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0056)
    - Broken Bottle Blues -- [Pix], undated; ID: 203.0048 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0048)
    - Cars and Band, undated; ID: 203.0039 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0039)
    - CBGB New Year's Eve, 1978; ID: 203.0112A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0112A)
    - CBGB New Year's Eve, Part II, 1978; ID: 203.0113 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0113)
    - CBGB Original Negative Dailies, undated; ID: 203.0182A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0182A)
    - "Clean" -- [Mag], undated; ID: 203.0111 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0111)
    - [Compilation Reel: "Naked Pregnant Woman, Etc.", undated; ID: 203.0185 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0185)
    - [Compilation Reel with Blondie Footage], undated; ID: 203.0184 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0184)
    - [Compilation Reel with Performance Footage], undated; ID: 203.0187 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0187)
    - [Concert Footage -- Night Lunch?], undated; ID: 203.0036 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0036)
    - Crazy Andy, undated; ID: 203.0019 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0019)
    - Easy on the Eyes -- [#7, Optical Track], undated; ID: 203.0052 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0052)
    - Easy on the Eyes -- [Pix], undated; ID: 203.0051 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0051)
    - The Foreigner -- ["B" Track, Reel 1], undated; ID: 203.0147A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0147A)
    - The Foreigner -- ["B" Track, Reel 2], undated; ID: 203.0148 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0148)
    - The Foreigner -- ["B" Track, Reel 3], undated; ID: 203.0149 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0149)
    - The Foreigner -- [Deleted from P1], undated; ID: 203.0125 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0125)
    - The Foreigner -- [Deleted from P1], undated; ID: 203.0126 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0126)
    - The Foreigner -- [Deleted from P1], undated; ID: 203.0127 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0127)
    - The Foreigner -- [Original Negative Outs], undated; ID: 203.0146 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0146)
    - The Foreigner -- [Original Negative Outs Reel #1 - 8], undated; ID: 203.0119 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0119)
    - The Foreigner -- [Original Negative Outs Reel #9 - 16], undated; ID: 203.0120 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0120)
    - The Foreigner -- [Original Negative Outs Reel #17 - 25], undated; ID: 203.0121 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0121)
    - The Foreigner -- [P1, "A" Roll], undated; ID: 203.0123A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0123A)
    - The Foreigner -- [P1, "B" Roll], undated; ID: 203.0124 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0124)
    - The Foreigner -- [P2, "A" Roll], undated; ID: 203.0128A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0128A)
    - The Foreigner -- [P2, "B" Roll], undated; ID: 203.0129 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0129)
    - The Foreigner -- [P3, "A" Roll], undated; ID: 203.0130A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0130A)
    - The Foreigner -- [P3, "B" Roll], undated; ID: 203.0131 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0131)
    - The Foreigner -- [Reel 3], undated; ID: 203.0183 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0183)
    - The Foreigner -- [Workpic Reel 1], undated; ID: 203.0132 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0132)
    - The Foreigner -- [Workpic Reel 2], undated; ID: 203.0133 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0133)
    - The Foreigner -- [Workpic Reel 3], undated; ID: 203.0134 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0134)
    - Frogs For Snakes -- Reel 1/6, undated; ID: 203.0140 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0140)
      Format: 35mm
    - Frogs For Snakes -- Reel 2/6, undated; ID: 203.0141 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0141)
    - Frogs For Snakes -- Reel 3/6, undated; ID: 203.0142 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0142)
    - Frogs For Snakes -- Reel 4/6, undated; ID: 203.0143 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0143)
    - Frogs For Snakes -- Reel 5/6, undated; ID: 203.0144 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0144)
    - Frogs For Snakes -- Reel 6/6, undated; ID: 203.0145 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0145)
    - Green Worm War -- [Negative], undated; ID: 203.0061A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0061A)
    - Green Worm War -- [Optical Track], undated; ID: 203.0062 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0062)
    - Heap #12 and #69, undated; ID: 203.0016 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0016)
    - High Flying Day -- [Original B + W], undated; ID: 203.0033 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0033)
    - High Flying Day -- [Sepia], undated; ID: 203.0034 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0034)
    - High Flying Day and We Meet Again -- [Track], undated; ID: 203.0037 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0037)
    - ["John the Cop"], 1996; ID: 203.0466 (Box 69, Media ID: 203.0466)
    - ["John the Cop" Roll No. 1 - 2], 1996; ID: 203.0467 (Box 69, Media ID: 203.0467)
    - Joni Mitchell in Concert, undated; ID: 203.0043 (Case 203.0043)
    - Millenium Madonna, undated; ID: 203.0055A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0055A)
    - [M & M Candies "Cowboy" through "Puppet On A Chain" TV Spot], undated; ID: 203.0203 - 203.0205 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0203 - 203.0205)
    - MROFNOC, undated; ID: 203.0032 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0032)
    - Muffins on Asphalt, undated; ID: 203.0005 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0005)
    - My, My Michaelangelo -- [Answer Print], ID: 203.0225 (Reel 203.0225)
    - My, My Michaelangelo -- [Release Print], ID: 203.0226 (Box Shared Fales 049, Reel 203.0226)
    - Night Lunch, undated; ID: 203.0011 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0011)
    - Nixon -- [Optical], undated; ID: 203.0007 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0007)
    - Nixon -- [Pix], undated; ID: 203.0006 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0006)
    - Nobody's Buried Here -- [Pix], undated; ID: 203.0047 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0047)
    - Only One Way Out -- [Optical Track], undated; ID: 203.0059 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0059)
    - Only One Way Out -- [Optical Track B Wind], undated; ID: 203.0058 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0058)
    - Only One Way Out -- [Pix], undated; ID: 203.0057 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0057)
    - Patti Smith -- ["B" Track, Space Raven], undated; ID: 203.0064 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0064)
    - Patti Smith -- [Mag Track], undated; ID: 203.0065A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0065A)
    - Patti Smith -- [Negative, Space Raven], undated; ID: 203.0063 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0063)
    - Patti Smith -- Outs, undated; ID: 203.0103 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0103)
    - Patti Smith -- [Outs, Mag Track], undated; ID: 203.0104 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0104)
    - Patti Smith -- ["Used" Mag Track], undated; ID: 203.0105 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0105)
    - Poe -- "E - 1130" [Original Negative], undated; ID: 203.0066A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0066A)
    - Poe -- "E - 1130" [Positive, 1 of 2], undated; ID: 203.0068 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0068)
    - Poe -- "E - 1130" [Positive, 2 of 2], undated; ID: 203.0067 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0067)
    - The Real McCoys: The Goodys Come to Town, undated; ID: 203.0030 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0030)
    - Refugee Girl -- [Music Track], undated; ID: 203.0109 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0109)
    - (With a) Refugee Girl -- [Pix], undated; ID: 203.0069 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0069)
    - (With a) Refugee Girl -- [Trk], undated; ID: 203.0070 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0070)
    - Reversal Positive -- March 10, 1978, ID: 203.0178A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0178A)
    - Scenes from Amos Poe, Pt. 1, undated; ID: 203.0083 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0083)
    - Scenes from Amos Poe, Pt. 2, undated; ID: 203.0084 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0084)
    - The Sheriff Slept Here, undated; ID: 203.0031 (Case 203.0031)
    - So Glad I Came -- [Pix], undated; ID: 203.0049 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0049)
    - So Glad I Came -- [Track], undated; ID: 203.0050 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0050)
    - Space, undated; ID: 203.0023A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0023A)
    - Space Raven, undated; ID: 203.0027 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0027)
    - Space Raven -- Patti Smith, undated; ID: 203.0162 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0162)
    - 1) St. Mark's Place Massacre 2) Ark of Destiny, undated; ID: 203.0002 (Case 203.0002)
    - 1) St. Mark's Place Massacre 2) Ark of Destiny -- [Internegative], undated; ID: 203.0097A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0097A)
    - 1) St. Mark's Place Massacre 2) Ark of Destiny -- [Internegative Answer Print], undated; ID: 203.0098 (Reel 203.0098)
    - 1) St. Mark's Place Massacre 2) Ark of Destiny -- [Release Print], undated; ID: 203.0099 (Box Shared Fales 060, Reel 203.0099)
    - Subway Riders -- [M Pix], undated; ID: 203.0165 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0165)
    - Talking 21st Century Blues, undated; ID: 203.0163 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0163)
    - Talking 21st Century Blues -- [Mag], undated; ID: 203.0096 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0096)
    - Tina + Buried Treasure, undated; ID: 203.0010 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0010)
    - Triple Bogey on a Five Par Hole, undated; ID: 203.0013 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0013)
    - Triple Bogey -- Checkprint Reel 1/5, undated; ID: 203.0135 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0135)
    - Triple Bogey -- Checkprint Reel 2/5, undated; ID: 203.0136 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0136)
    - Triple Bogey -- Checkprint Reel 3/5, undated; ID: 203.0137 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0137)
    - Triple Bogey -- Checkprint Reel 4/5, undated; ID: 203.0138 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0138)
    - Triple Bogey -- Checkprint Reel 5/5, undated; ID: 203.0139 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0139)
    - Triple Bogey -- [Mag, "Anf. R4"], undated; ID: 203.0029 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0029)
    - Triple Bogey -- [Mag, Roll 3 and 4], undated; ID: 203.0028 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0028)
    - Triple Bogey -- [Pull Ups Leader Only], undated; ID: 203.0188 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0188)
    - Triple Bogey -- Single Strand Reel 1/10 [Original Color, B + W Negative], undated; ID: 203.0152A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0152A)
    - Triple Bogey -- Single Strand Reel 2/10 [Original Color, B + W Negative], undated; ID: 203.0153A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0153A)
    - Triple Bogey -- Single Strand Reel 3/10 [Original Color, B + W Negative], undated; ID: 203.0154A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0154A)
    - Triple Bogey -- Single Strand Reel 4/10 [Original Color, B + W Negative], undated; ID: 203.0155A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0155A)
    - Triple Bogey -- Single Strand Reel 5/10 [Original Color, B + W Negative], undated; ID: 203.0156A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0156A)
    - Triple Bogey -- Single Strand Reel 6/10 [Original Color, B + W Negative], undated; ID: 203.0157A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0157A)
    - Triple Bogey -- Single Strand Reel 7/10 [Original Color, B + W Negative], undated; ID: 203.0158A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0158A)
    - Triple Bogey -- Single Strand Reel 8/10 [Original Color, B + W Negative], undated; ID: 203.0159A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0159A)
    - Triple Bogey -- Single Strand Reel 9/10 [Original Color, B + W Negative], undated; ID: 203.0160A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0160A)
    - Triple Bogey -- Single Strand Reel 10/10 [Original Color, B + W Negative], undated; ID: 203.0161A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0161A)
    - Triple Bogey -- [TRK Negative, Reel 1/10], undated; ID: 203.0166 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0166)
    - Triple Bogey -- [TRK Negative, Reel 2/10], undated; ID: 203.0167 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0167)
    - Triple Bogey -- [TRK Negative, Reel 3/10], undated; ID: 203.0168 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0168)
    - Triple Bogey -- [TRK Negative, Reel 4/10], undated; ID: 203.0169 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0169)
    - Triple Bogey -- [TRK Negative, Reel 5/10], undated; ID: 203.0170 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0170)
    - Triple Bogey -- [TRK Negative, Reel 6/10], undated; ID: 203.0171 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0171)
    - Triple Bogey -- [TRK Negative, Reel 7/10], undated; ID: 203.0172 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0172)
    - Triple Bogey -- [TRK Negative, Reel 8/10], undated; ID: 203.0173 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0173)
    - Triple Bogey -- [TRK Negative, Reel 9/10], ID: 203.0174 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0174)
    - Triple Bogey -- [TRK Negative, Reel 10/10], undated; ID: 203.0175 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0175)
    - [Two Adult Movie Excerpts], undated; ID: 203.0189 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0189)
    - [Unidentified Amos Poe -- 16mm B + W Reversal], undated; ID: 203.0038 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0038)
    - [Unidentified Amos Poe -- 16mm Film], undated; ID: 203.0017 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0017)
    - [Unidentified Amos Poe -- 16mm Film], undated; ID: 203.0018 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0018)
    - [Unidentified Amos Poe -- 16mm Film], undated; ID: 203.0020 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0020)
    - [Unidentified Amos Poe -- 16mm Film], undated; ID: 203.0022 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0022)
    - [Unidentified Amos Poe -- 16mm Film], undated; ID: 203.0024 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0024)
    - [Unidentified Amos Poe -- 16mm Mag Track], undated; ID: 203.0025 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0025)
    - [Unidentified Amos Poe -- 16mm Positive], undated; ID: 203.0026 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0026)
    - [Unidentified Ending Credit through Street Scape Footage], undated; ID: 203.0206 - 203.0215 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0206 - 203.0215)
    - [Unidentified -- Reversal Positive], undated; ID: 203.0179 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0179)
    - [Unidentified Super 8 Films], undated; ID: 203.0014 (Case 203.0014)
    - [Unidentified -- Track Negative], undated; ID: 203.0180 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0180)
    - [Unidentified -- Unmade Beds Related Title], undated; ID: 203.0181 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0181)
    - [Unknown: Manhattan and Brooklyn Bridge Footage], undated; ID: 203.0190 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0190)
    - Unmade Beds, undated; ID: 203.0150 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0150)
    - Unmade Beds, undated; ID: 203.0151 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0151)
    - Unmade Beds -- "Drunk Scene - Not Sync" -- [Mag], undated; ID: 203.0090 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0090)
    - Unmade Beds -- Outtakes, undated; ID: 203.0110 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0110)
    - Unmade Beds -- [Pix], undated; ID: 203.0053 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0053)
    - Unmade Beds, Pt. 1 -- "A" Roll, undated; ID: 203.0071A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0071A)
    - Unmade Beds, Pt. 1 -- "B" Roll, undated; ID: 203.0072 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0072)
    - Unmade Beds, Pt. 2 -- "A" Roll, undated; ID: 203.0073A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0073A)
    - Unmade Beds, Pt. 2 -- "B" Roll, undated; ID: 203.0074 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0074)
    - Unmade Beds, Pt. 3 -- "A" Roll, undated; ID: 203.0075A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0075A)
    - Unmade Beds, Pt. 3 -- "B" Roll, undated; ID: 203.0076 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0076)
    - Unmade Beds -- Reel 1 [Composite Print], undated; ID: 203.0093 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0093)
    - Unmade Beds -- Reel 1 [Mag], undated; ID: 203.0087 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0087)
    - Unmade Beds -- [Mag Track], undated; ID: 203.0054 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0054)
    - Unmade Beds -- Reel 1 [Voice Track], undated; ID: 203.0079 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0079)
    - Unmade Beds -- Reel 1 [Work Print], undated; ID: 203.0085 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0085)
    - Unmade Beds -- Reel 2 [Composite Print], undated; ID: 203.0094 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0094)
    - Unmade Beds -- Reel 2 [Mix Mag], undated; ID: 203.0088 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0088)
    - Unmade Beds -- Reel 2 [Music Track], undated; ID: 203.0082 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0082)
    - Unmade Beds -- Reel 2 [Voice Track], undated; ID: 203.0081 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0081)
    - Unmade Beds -- Reel 3 [Composite Print], undated; ID: 203.0095 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0095)
    - Unmade Beds -- Reel 3 [Mix Mag], undated; ID: 203.0089 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0089)
    - Unmade Beds -- Reel 7 [Music Track], undated; ID: 203.0080 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0080)
    - Unmade Beds -- [Unidentified Mag], undated; ID: 203.0091 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0091)
    - Unmade Beds -- [Unidentified Mag], undated; ID: 203.0092 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0092)
    - Unmade Beds, Work Pix -- Reel 2, undated; ID: 203.0078 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0078)
    - Unmade Beds, Work Pix -- Reel 3, undated; ID: 203.0077 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0077)
    - Unmade Beds -- Work Print, undated; ID: 203.0086 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0086)
    - [Unprocessed Unidentified 16mm], undated; ID: 203.0468 (Box 69, Media ID: 203.0468)
    - [Unidentified 8mm Film], undated; ID: 203.0469 (Box 69, Media ID: 203.0469)
      Format: 8mm
    - [Untitled NY Footage with "Night Lunch" Marquee], undated; ID: 203.0164 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0164)
    - Various Fluxus Films, c1966; ID: 203.0015 (Case 203.0015)
    - Wasted Visions, undated; ID: 203.0004 (Case 203.0004)
    - Wayne City Show, undated; ID: 203.0186 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0186)
    - We Meet Again, undated; ID: 203.0035 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0035)
    - 1) What is Life 2) She Wore a Red Ribbon, undated; ID: 203.0003 (Case 203.0003)
    - Where am I, Where are You, undated; ID: 203.0040 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0040)
    - Where am I, Where are You, undated; ID: 203.0041 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0041)
    - Z Blue -- [B + W Original Negative], undated; ID: 203.0176A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0176A)
    - Z Blue -- [B + W Positive], undated; ID: 203.0177 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0177)
  - Series VIII, Subseries C: Film Documentation
    - Laboratory Forms, 1975 - 1978, 1990 - 1991, 2009 (Box 44)
      This is a collection of 35 production files preserving inspection forms, time strips, lighting charts, and other laboratory notes removed from Poe's original filmic elements.
- Series IX: Video
  - Series IX, Subseries A: Access Copies
    - [1]-- Ballad of a Thin Woman [2]-- Knife in the Rain, [1972]; ID: 203.0221 (Box Shared Fales 143, Dvd 203.0221)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Format: DVD
    - [1]-- St. Mark's Place Massacre [2]-- Ark of Destiny, [1972]; ID: 203.0218 (Box Shared Fales 143, Dvd 203.2018)
    - My, My Michaelangelo, 1974; ID: 203.0229 (Box Shared Fales 143, Dvd 203.0229)
    - Unmade Beds, 1976; ID: 203.0232 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 203.0232)
      Format: VHS
      Duration: 00:77:00
      Content: A film by Amos Poe
      Starring Duncan Hannah, Debbie Harry
      This is the story of Rico, a man who lives in New York in 1976 but who lives his own life in Paris during the time of the 'New Wave'.
    - CBGB's Second Avenue Theater - Film Footage - Reel One, December, 1978; ID: 203.0474 (Box Shared Fales 143, Dvd 203.0474)
      Duration: 00:37:45
      Silent film footage shot at CBGB's Second Avenue Theater, December 1978. May be multiple nights. Performers include: Patti Smith, The Dictators, Richard Hell and the Voidoids, and The Shirts.
    - CBGB's Second Avenue Theater - Film Footage - Reel Two, [December, 1978]; ID: 302.0477 (Box Shared Fales 143, Dvd 203.0477)
      Black and White, Silent
      Duration: 00:03:00
      Unidentified performers - onstage and backstage footage
    - CBGB's Second Avenue Theater - Film Footage - Edited Excerpt, December, 1978; ID: 203.0480 (Box Shared Fales 143, Dvd 203.0480)